um I think he stated we would pretty
heavily invest on this side of the
football. So I think between um some of
our acquisitions in the off season and
then you know these first three picks
which you know not necessarily how we
thought it would play out. Um it sort of
just matches that theme and I think
what's beautiful about is all three of
these guys it's not something that we
felt like we reached for. Um, you know,
we we made the trade back and with our
first pick and showed a lot of patience
uh with the next two and still got two
really really good players. So excited
about the group. Um, still have a lot of
work to do with two picks today as it
sits right now and um, you know, ready
to go. So with that, I'll take
questions.
>> It's it's kind of unusual to go back to
back wide receiver. You guys had all
night to think about this pick. Was he
prominent all night? Yeah, I think it's
just like I said as as we set as we took
a step back when as all teams do um when
the first round ends and and look at
your board, it it sort of just, you
know, stuck out to us. Like I said, you
know, we didn't necessarily plan to take
two receivers back to back, but we also
uh couldn't ignore value and again
wanted to make sure that we invested on
offense, gave Todd and the offensive
coaches uh the resources they need to
work with. And and I mean the two
players not only uh fit that bill, but
they they complement
really really well
>> almost like stealing getting Denzel at
that point.
>> I mean I would I wouldn't say that but
we definitely are excited. Like I said
we you know we had to show patience uh
because you know you just get antsy when
you see a guy that you think has a ton
of ability. You know he's big, he has
great hands. Um you know very subtle
sneaky speed uh and just really really
complements things that we we have in
that room right now. And you just have
to exude exude some some patience and
allow it to come to you. and and we're
excited uh that you know we necessarily
have to give up any resources to get a
player of his caliber.
>> What do these two picks say, Glenn,
about the way you guys assessed the wide
receiver room after 2025?
>> Yeah, I think it it it it doesn't
necessarily only speak to the room, but
also just speaks to the two players. Um
Casey's really explosive. He's really
talented. We love what he can do with
the football. Um and then Denzel, you
know, almost 6'4, 215. Um very physical,
competitive, and has great hands. And so
I I think it's it's it's just as much
about what we're adding and we're always
talking about is it's you know this is a
team building exercise not a player
acquisition exercise and we're happy
with with the the two skill sets that we
added
>> in terms of
>> Go ahead. Go ahead.
>> Okay. like you mentioned with his size
and the 5050 ball ability that he has
like how much are you guys hoping that
he can be an immediate sort of red zone
threat as a
>> look I all these guys
he has is a great foundation it's those
different skill sets that you spoke
trust
and and the rest of the offensive staff
CJ room to to put them in the right spot
and our biggest focus, let's give them
as much talent, um, as much versatility
and and allow them to do their jobs.
>> Now, in general,
>> kind of talk about what how wellrounded.
>> Yeah, I think that's a fair question. At
the end of the day, we we, you know, we
talk about this, we want to add
competition, you know, so this is a top
tier offense in the NFL. You know, we
want the cream to rise to the top. And
so, um, you know, we definitely believe
we have talent in the room. Jerry Judy
is still a talent NFL, but um we're also
not be complacent and push ourselves to
keep making sure that we have what we
need to be the type of offense we want
to.
>> When there was uh reports uh the
beginning of the night about the Browns
talking about moving up in this round,
uh if that's true, was it for Boston or
someone else?
>> I mean, I can't speak specific to what
you're saying. I mean, we there's
multiple conversations going on. I mean,
we had conversations about every
direction, you know, moving up, sitting
still, moving back. So, I think that's
just a part of, you know, managing, you
know, our position on the board and and
trying to get a feel for what what's
happening in front of us and behind us.
So, I mean, like I said, I I don't know
specifically what you're talking about,
but yeah, I mean, we're we're we're
always on the phone. I probably have to
go back up and get on the phone again.
Um, so that's just a part of it. Tony,
what's
>> the collaboration like with, you know,
Coach Mon? We saw the video, you know,
fist bump from Andrew for making the
Boston pick. But, you know, you worked
with Kevin for six years and now you're
you're working with Todd. So, just what
what's that collaboration been like?
>> Yeah. Know, I think um I think Todd, as
as you all probably know, are getting a
sense of, he's he's very direct and he's
very clear about what he wants and what
he needs. I think you have a good sense
of how each skill set will fit into um
the system and and the scheme. And so,
uh, throughout the process in the
spring, just across all the receivers
and a lot of the offensive players, you
know, I thought our offensive coaches
gave us a really good picture of one,
what we needed. Um, and then also two,
just as a respect to each player, um,
how they would use them. And that just
makes it a lot clearer for Andrew and
just our staff as a group to walk into
it saying, "Hey, if we take this player
here or if we take this specific player,
this is how they're going to be deployed
in our offense." And feel good about it,
you know? So, I think he gave us a good
picture for both players, KC and and and
um Denzo.
>> I know that you haven't you've invested
in receiver in other ways, right? Trey,
but this is the highest this regime has
taken form receiver, let alone two. Was
there something different
philosophically or in the approach this
draft that led you to the receiver so
high?
>> Honestly, no. You know, like you one,
you always sat back and assess what you
can do better, you know, just within the
job. So yeah, you know, we definitely
looked at just across all our picks. Um,
you know, and then we do that every
year. How can we be better? What did we
miss? What did we hit on, etc. But, um,
you know, some of it is one, you know,
we just had higher picks, you know, for
the second year in a row. Uh, and then
it's also just the quality of the
players that we were sitting and looking
at, um, at this spot. So, I wouldn't say
there was a wholesale uh, change to how
we approached it, but you definitely
have to step back and assess yourself.
So, at all in discussion at 24.
>> I mean, I won't I'm not going to get
into that. I think, you know, I don't
want to make it a CC versus Boston
thing. Um,
>> yeah. Well, yeah. What it is is we
trusted the board. Um, you know, we we
think a lot about Denzel's talent and
his ability. I think a lot of teams
probably had him with a with a first
round or really high up. So, you know,
we're just excited that we had the
chance to still get them where we're
sitting at.
going through everything and the, you
know, simulations of your board, you can
try to predict as best you can following
your data and everything, but how
surprised were you that Denzel felt to
you guys right there and you get your
two big wide receivers that are rated
high back to back?
>> Uh, I mean, to your point, you can
simulate it as much as you can, and we
do. I mean, we probably spent four plus
hours going through a number of
iterations and you still don't get
through all of them, right? You you
still can't uh
100% pinpoint how it's going to play
out. There's probably a few picks in the
first round that even with those number
of iterations that we we went through,
you know, sort of caught us off guard.
So, we try to get as close as possible
and and I think what it does help us do
is have good answers to the tests when
they come. And so, hey, if we do get a
scenario that's within this this
ballpark, this is how we would play it
out. And I think this is close to maybe
one or two of them that we work through.
Um, just just glad we got them. You
know,
>> being in a situation where you have
Casey and Denzel.
>> Did I Did we ever envision it? Sure.
Yeah, I think we did envision it. you
know, uh, to tell you that that we were
very certain that it would happen, I
don't I don't know that we could tell
you that, but we definitely it's
definitely something you you think about
just in terms of how you build the team,
how you build a roster, you know, when
you get to pick 39, is this something
you would do where you take two
receivers back to back?
>> What did you
talk to?
So, it was it was pretty interesting
because both he and Casey were together,
you know, and so um you know, you have
now that I look back, both guys are
sitting at dinner and you're getting to
know the two different personalities and
getting to understand, uh who they are
as humans and young men and so much
about their life. And I mean, Denzel's
um academic all Big 10 um you know, an
exceptional kid, you know, loves the
game and and has a lot ahead in his
future. Same thing with KC. just just
hilarious, funny, a lot of, you know, a
lot of energy, but also very competitive
and just when you spoke to football
things, he definitely, you know, flips a
switch and and you love to see that
about him. So, uh, looking back, like I
said, to the question that was just
asked, couldn't have envisioned that
both players as we sit there at dinner
would be on our roster, but but it's
also a thing that I'm not not mad about.
>> Where was that dinner?
>> It's just our 30 visits. Yeah. So, as
when we take him out to eat,
>> I know lots of talk about Casey's
ability on punt returns, but Denzel can
also Yeah, he did.
>> I mean, just how much, you know, did
that kind of add add value to
>> We It's in the back of our minds. We
know it, right? Like, there's it just
adds it's an added luxury to have
players who can, you know, with with the
constraints of of the 53man roster and
the guys you can have active to have
someone, especially with his dimensions
and build to go back and field punts.
like it's, you know, we're definitely um
fortunate that he also can do that. Our
focus is on his ability at receiver.
Same thing with KC. Um and but again, it
is it is an added bonus. I should have
mentioned that early, but that's a good
good point.
>> Everyone assume that offensive line by
receiver in the first round were the top
priorities and obviously that's the
direction you want. Now, Andrew Barry
mentioned yesterday he expects this to
be a volume draft for you guys. Wants to
bring in a pretty good size rookie
class. Do you feel like now you guys are
in a spot where you can kind of start
stacking the roster? You don't
necessarily have to maybe zero in on
needs
a as much maybe as you might have in the
first.
>> Yeah, I hope so. And also, I mean, I
wouldn't say we we you know, we're we're
cornered into to zero in on these as
well with the first couple, you know,
like again, we end up taking two
receivers, but uh we have eight picks, I
believe, and um have two more tonight at
minimum. And I think it is an
opportunity to just continue to add guys
who will come in and compete um at in
different roles on different sides of
the football on both sides of the
football. So uh yeah,
it it was important for us not to to
move too many picks because we want the
volume um and and we felt like we we
needed it. So uh we definitely are
excited about the position that we're in
after having three picks in the first,
you know, in the top 50 and still more
to go. It's it's pretty when when you
guys hired Todd when he first got here
and he kind of talked to you about what
his sort of vision was for the offense.
Not that you could predict that what
exactly what's going to happen on on
draft night like you mentioned. Um but
is this like pretty close to in terms of
the resources you guys have used what
that kind of vision what you guys
thought that vision could be in terms of
addressing the offensive line,
addressing wide receiver?
>> Sure. But I also think like the the
number one thing and I think you guys
may have heard him say this is nothing
getting in the way of winning. And I
think he approaches coaching and and
calling the game that way. Uh he will
have two tight ends on the field, three
tight ends on the field, uh four
receivers, uh different packages, run,
you know, run the quarterback. Um get
feed feed the guy who's having a great
game. I think Todd is is so diverse in
his approach and so open-minded when it
comes to how to move the football down
the field and score points because at
the end of the day, that's what we're
trying to do. Uh it from a 30,000 foot
view, it just opened up our opportunity
across all the players in the draft
because you just know um you're not
necessarily pigeonholed into it has to
be X skill set, X makeup. It's really
like, hey, have a good idea of how we
want to use this guy. Todd will take it
from there. So, it was more so probably
from that lens as opposed to the
specific like skill sets receiver or
running back or tight end or O line if
that answers.
>> Appreciate you.